&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在本单元的最后一次练习中，我们将查看和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: In our final exercise of this unit, we're gonna look at and
使用class关键字进行练习。
practice with the class keyword.
您将把名称空间对象重构为使用类系统。
You're going to be refactoring a namespace object into using a class system.
因此，如果您有一个带有this aware编码的命名空间模式，并且
So if you had a namespace pattern with the this aware coding and
您希望改为使用类语法来尝试组织该代码，
you wanted to instead use the class syntax to try to organize that code,
然后我们将把它重构成类语法。
then we're gonna be refactoring it into that class syntax.
特别是在这里，我们将利用类扩展。
In particular, here, we're gonna take advantage of the class extends.
所以有几个功能
So there are a couple of functions
在此命名空间的定义中不知道这一点。
within the definition of this namespace that are not this aware.
他们没有理由特别关注
And there's no reason for them to be specifically on
这个我们称之为工作坊的特殊物体。
this particular object that we're calling workshop.
他们本质上是帮手。
They are essentially helpers.
所以我们要做的是有一个名为helpers的父类。
So what we're gonna do is have a parent class called helpers.
然后，我们将有一个扩展帮助器的子类，并且
And then, we're gonna have a child class that extends helpers, and
那个儿童班就是那个将被称为工作坊的班级
that child class is the one that's gonna be called workshop, and
它将继承这些帮助者。
it will inherit those helpers.
所以换句话说，
So in other words,
它将通过继承组成以访问这些帮助者。
it will compose through inheritance to have access to those helpers.
而那些人不需要被如此束缚，因为他们并没有意识到这一点。
And those won't need to be this bound, because they aren't this aware.
如果您查看ex JS，您会注意到您有一个名称空间对象。
If you look at the EX JS, you'll notice that you have a namespaced object.
所有方法前面都有这个点引用。
All the methods with all the this dot references in front of them.
而且你确实有一些地方你的函数并没有意识到这一点，所以
And you do have some places where you have functions that are not this aware, so
他们没有被捆绑。
they're not bound.
但是你还有其他的地方可以约束他们，而且
But you have other places where they are bound, and
你需要确保一旦你连接了一个类系统，这些仍然可以工作。
you need to make sure that those are still working once you wire up a class system.
所以这里的想法是不是在一个对象上定义所有这些东西，
So the idea here is instead of defining all these things on an object,
您将在一个类中将所有这些定义为方法，并且
you're gonna be defining all of these as methods in a class, and
然后实例化该类并使用它。
then instantiating that class and using it.
这就是课堂练习的内容。
So that's the substance of the exercise on class.
我们将在几分钟后回来讨论该解决方案。
We'll be back in a few minutes to talk through that solution.
一如既往，如果你卡住了
As always, if you get stuck and
你需要一个提示，你可以检查出解决方案在EX点固定文件。
you need a hint, you can check out the solution in the ex dot fixed file.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：所以听起来像是要分解成这些感知对象，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So it sounds like for breaking down into this aware objects,
基本原理不是关于大小和可读性，而是
the rationale is less about size and readability and
更多关于分离关注点的地方，你会想要每一个，有点-
more about the separation of concerns where you would want each, kind of-
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yes.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：好的，酷。你回到指导逻辑
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Okay, cool. You going back to the guiding logic
结构的，对象开始和结束的位置。
of the structuring, where an object begins and ends for this composition.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的。&gt；&gt；发言人2：这个代表团。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: This delegation.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我认为这是真实的，完全独立于你是选择还是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think that's true entirely separate of whether you choose or
您可以选择类，或者选择模块，或者
you choose classes or you choose modules or
你可以选择其他的组织模式。
you choose some other organization pattern.
我认为你应该问什么在逻辑上可以结合在一起
I think you should be asking what logically fits together and
试着拥有最小的碎片。
try to have the smallest pieces.
我的意思是，我不一定总是喜欢单一责任原则，
I mean, I don't necessarily always go to like the single responsibility principle,
但这是一个合理的方向，对吗？
but that is a reasonable place to head towards, right?
把这看作是一个指导原则是合理的。
It's reasonable to think about that as like a guiding principle.
如果这个东西在做一堆不同的事情，也许那应该
That if this thing is doing a bunch of different stuff, maybe that should
只是做几件不同的事情，做那些不同的作品。
just be several different things doing those different pieces.